Viewers all over the world, this is the time we have been praying for.
I want you to know that your situation as a Christian is merely a short break between two events.
Your situation, my situation, whatever situation I am in, is merely a short break between two events.
This is the time we have been praying for. Are you ready?
Right now, it is time to get rid of any spirit that is not of God, that is tormenting your life.
Your body is the temple of God.
That nightmare in your business, nightmare in your health, nightmare in your marriage,
nightmare in your family, nightmare in your career, nightmare in your destiny - nightmare is demon.
Viewers, open your lips and begin to rebuke that nightmare in your business, nightmare in your health,
nightmare in your family and nightmare in your marriage,
nightmare in your career.
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch The Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
In Jesus Christ's name we pray.
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch The Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Demon is nightmare
I said, demon - evil spirit that torments your life, your career, your health - is nightmare.
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch The Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
We come against you, in the name of Jesus!
Viewers at home, wherever you are, begin to come against demons!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch The Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Viewers, come on, let us believe together.
Let me thank Jesus for giving you faith to believe.
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch The Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Lord, remove whatever disease, sickness, affliction in their blood, fluids, tendons.
Be removed, in the name of Jesus!
Remove that cancer, in the name of Jesus!
Remove that disease in their blood, in the name of Jesus!
Remove that disease in their liver, in the name of Jesus!
Remove that disease in their kidneys, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch The Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Wherever that affliction, be removed in the name of Jesus!
Be removed in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch The Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Be removed in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch The Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Remove that affliction, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch The Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
That mountain, that nightmare, be removed in the name of Jesus!
Viewers, yes, I want to congratulate you because you are a successful person;
you are a healed person, in the name of Jesus Christ.